Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2019 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence, 1964-2013; 172383
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence, 190087
    - Henes, Donna and Daile Kaplan, 1990, undated; 205765 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Henry [Story], 1984; 205766 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Hensala, Craig, 1997; 205767 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - [Herb], 1978; 205768 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Heresies Magazine, 1986; 205769 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Herlin, Jean-Noël, 1988; 205770 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Herman, Shirley, 1987-1994; 205771 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Hero, Barbara, 1977; 205772 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Hewson, Federico, 2001-2007; 205773 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Heyward, Julia, 2005-2006, undated; 205774 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Higgins, Diane, 1991; 205775 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Higgs, Kimball, 1989; 205776 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - High Performance, undated; 205777 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Hijuelos, Joseph, 1983-1985; 205778 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Hilary, 1993; 205779 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Hileman, Jayne, 1977; 205780 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Hill, Leslie and Helen Paris, 2001; 205781 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Hill, Murray, 1997-2005; 205782 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Hillerbrand, Cathy, undated; 205783 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - [Him], undated; 205784 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Hirano, Michiko, 2001; 205785 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Hirschy, David and Chris, 1976-1989, undated; 205786 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - HO, undated; 205787 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Ho, Dennia, 2005; 205788 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Hodges, Jeanne/NEA, 1989; 205789 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Hoff, Pat, 2008; 205790 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Hoffberg, Judy, 1976; 205791 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Hoffman, Barbara, 1999; 205792 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Hoffstein, Murray M.D., 1982-1985; 205793 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Hogan. Matthew, 1997; 205794 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Holden, Barry/Prentice and Chan, Ohlhausen LLP, 1996; 205795 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Holland, DK, undated; 205796 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Holland, Sarah, 1984-1987; 205797 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Holst, Lisa/ Emerson Gallery, 1998; 205798 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Holstein, Pieter, 1978-2005, undated; 205799 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Holtz, Helmuth, 1975; 205800 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - [Holzer], 1979; 205801 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Honeymoon Miralda Project, 1987; 205802 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Hořejš, Vit, 1997; 205803 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Horn, Stuart, undated; 205804 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Horschak, Amy, 1998; 205805 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Howard, 1977-1998, undated; 205806 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Howard, 1978; 205807 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Howard, Barbara, 1978; 205808 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Howard, David, 1988; 205809 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Howland, Rebecca (Becky), 1994; 205810 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Hsieh, Teh-Ching and Qin Qin, 2005; 205814 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Hsieh, Teh Ching, 1984-2007; 205811 (Box 12, Folder 78)
      Poster materials sent by Hsieh can be found in the oversize series.
    - Hsieh, Teh-Ching and Linda Montano, undated; 205812 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Hsieh, Teh-Ching and [Maureen], undated; 205813 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Hugh Hefner First Amendment Awards, 1991; 205815 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Hui, Tammy, undated; 205816 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Huisman, Hetty, undated; 205817 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Hunt, Diane, 2000; 205818 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Hutchins, Alice, 1985-1997; 205819 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Hutchins, Alice and Jack, 1984; 205820 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Hwang, Koosil-ja, 2002; 205821 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Hydler, Glenda, 1985-2006, undated; 205822 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Hyson, Sharon, 1978; 205823 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - I., undated; 205824 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Alex I [ ], 2002; 205825 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Ida, undated; 205826 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Ifill, [Natsee], 1984; 205827 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - illegible, 205828 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - illegible, 205829 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Imani, undated; 205830 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Independent Television Service, 1992; 205831 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Ingberman, Jeanette/ Exit Art, 1985-2007; 205832 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Ingberman, Jeanette and Papo Colo/ Exit Art, 1990, 1998, undated; 205833 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Ingrid, undated; 205834 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Innocent, Fritz, 2000; 205835 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Inoue, Yoko, 2007, undated; 205836 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Interaction Arts/ Alexander M. Plague, Jr., 1982; 205837 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - IRS, 1988-1989; 205838 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Irina, 1999; 205839 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Irock, Pansy, undated; 205840 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Irwin, Kim, 1994-2005; 205841 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Isabel, 1989; 205842 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Isabel, 1984-2002; 205843 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Islip Art Museum, Cohalan, Mary Lou and Catherine Valenza, 1991-1998; 205844 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - J., 1996; 205845 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - J.C., 1991; 205846 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Jack, Elizabeth and Shawn, 1979; 205847 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Jacks, Robert, 1998; 205848 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Jackson, Homer, 1984; 205849 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Jacobs, Gundula and Ted, 1989; 205850 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Jacobsen, Carol, 1986-1994; 205851 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Jacquin, Jeff and Gwen, undated; 205852 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Judrunka and Darko, 2000; 205853 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Jaime, 2002; 205854 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Jajich, Audrey, undated; 205855 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Jakovljevic, Branislav, 2002; 205856 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - James, Ed, 1984; 206033 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - James A. Michener Arts Center, 1988; 206034 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Jon, 1973; 206035 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Jane, 1978; 206036 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Jane, undated; 206037 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Janet, 1984, undated; 206038 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Janeway, Michael/NAJP, 2002; 206039 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Jankovic, Radmila-Iva, 2005; 206040 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Jarden, Richards, 1976-2007, undated; 205857 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Jarden, Marcia and Richards, 1977; 205858 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Jardin, Fred, date illegible; 205859 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Jaxson, Carrie, 2005; 205860 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Jean, undated; 205861 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Jeanette, undated; 205862 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Jeannie, 1991; 205863 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Jeff and Bob, 2000; 205864 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Jehu, Ron, 1976; 205865 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Jen and Josh, 2004; 205866 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Jen/Thundergulch, 2001; 205867 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Jenness, Morgan, 1995; 205868 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Jennifer, 1996; 205869 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Jennifer, undated; 205870 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Jenny, 1985; 205871 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Jenny, undated; 205872 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Jerome Foundation, 1982; 205873 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Jessica, 1992; 205874 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Jessica and Kerinia, undated; 205875 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Jill, undated; 205876 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Jill, undated; 205877 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Jim, undated; 205878 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Uncle Jim and Aunt Marge, undated; 205879 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Jimbo, 1993; 205880 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Jo, 1995; 205881 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - [Joan and Jolin], undated; 205882 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Joanne and Lew, 2005; 205883 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Joanne, Mike, Meredith and Brian, undated; 205884 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Jody, date illegible; 205885 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Joe, 2005, undated; 205886 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - John, 1979; 205887 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - John, 1981; 205888 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - John, undated; 205889 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - John, undated; 205890 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - John and Susan [Gr...], 1975-1978, undated; 205891 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Johnny, 1962; 205892 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Johnny, undated; 205893 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Johnson, Anne, 1989; 205894 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Johnson, Emma, 1999; 205895 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Johnson, Joyce and Marc, 1996; 205896 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Johnson, Rhonda, undated; 205897 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Jon, 2000; 205898 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Jon and Carol, undated; 205899 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Jon and Vernita, 1990; 205900 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - Jones, Amelia, 2007; 205901 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Jones, Baird, 1996; 205902 (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - Jones, Canby, 1967; 205903 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - Jones, Kathy Ann, 1991; 205904 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Jones, Sabrina, 2000-2002; 205905 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Jordan, Michael, 1985; 205906 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Jordan-Hayes, Nikki and Michael, undated; 205907 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Joy, 1988; 205908 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Joy and John, 1997; 205909 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Joyce K., 1988; 205910 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Juan G., 1981-1985; 205911 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Judy and David, 1987; 205912 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - Judy, ca. 1989; 205913 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Julia, 1977; 205914 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Julie, 1986; 205915 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Julie, Undated; 205916 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Julie and Glenn, 2007-2008; 205917 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - K., 1978-1981; 205918 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - K. B., 2002; 205919 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - K Brew, 1998; 205920 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - K., Constantine, 1999; 205921 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Kahane, Lisa, 2000; 205922 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Kahn, Robin, 1988; 205923 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Kamen, Steven, Genisia, Anna and Emily, 1999-2001; 205924 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Kane, Louisa / Management Consultants for the Arts, Inc., 1992; 205925 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Kaneshiro, Cheryl; Toporowicz, Maciek, Undated; 205926 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - Kanter, Norbert, 2001; 205927 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Kapadia, Heena; Morris, Ted, 1999; 205928 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Kaplan, Daile, 1978-2001; Undated; 205929 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - Kaplan, Janet, 2005; 205930 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - Kaplan, Karen / The Rockefeller Foundation, 1995; 205931 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Kaplan, Steven, 1988; 205932 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Kaps, Amy, 1985; 205933 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - Karalis, Constantine, 1989; 205934 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Karen, 1978; 205935 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Karen, 1985; 205936 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Karin and Jonathan, 2004; 205937 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - Karla, 1989; 205938 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Karoly, Tardos, 2005; 205939 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Kasper, 1998; Undated; 205940 (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - Katchen, Michael; Varni, Suzanne, 1987-2007; 205941 (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Kate, 2005; 205942 (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - Kathy, 1977; 205943 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - Katie, Don, and Nathaniel, 1992-1996; 205944 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Katzowitz, Lauren, 1996; 205945 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Kaufmann / Joroff, 1992-2004; Undated; 205946 (Box 13, Folder 125)
    - Kawamata. Tadashi, 1986-1992; 205947 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - Kaz, Donna, 2000; 205948 (Box 13, Folder 127)
    - Keepers of the Waters, 2001-2002; 205949 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - Keith, Jon, Undated; 205950 (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - Kendall, Sherwood M., 1976; 205951 (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Kennedy, Katy, 2001; Undated; 205952 (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - Kennedy, Meaghan, 2004; 205953 (Box 13, Folder 132)
    - Kenneth, 1976-1979; Undated; 205954 (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - Kenny, Kay / Heresies, 1986; 205955 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - Kern, William Bliem, 1978; 205956 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - Kerrin, Jessica, 1994-1995; 205957 (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - Kershbaumer, Sharon, 1979-1988; 205958 (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - Khanna, Shama, 2007; 205959 (Box 13, Folder 138)
    - Killacky, John, Undated; 205960 (Box 13, Folder 139)
    - Kim, 1999; 205961 (Box 13, Folder 140)
    - Kim, Undated; 205962 (Box 13, Folder 141)
    - Kimbro, Ernestine, 1993-2007; 205963 (Box 13, Folder 142)
    - Kindred, Audrey, 2001; 205964 (Box 13, Folder 143)
    - King Tut [Crawford, Pepper], 1964-1965; 205965 (Box 13, Folder 144)
    - Kings County Clerk, 1990; 205966 (Box 13, Folder 145)
    - Kinsman, Eric, 1988; 205987 (Box 13, Folder 146)
    - Kipperman, Deanna/Marvin Shoes, undated; 205988 (Box 13, Folder 147)
    - Kitchel, Nancy, 1977; 205989 (Box 13, Folder 148)
    - Klayman, Melinda, 1990-1998, undated; 205990 (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Klein, Mary, 1998; 205991 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Klick, Laurel, 1977-1992; 205992 (Box 13, Folder 151)
    - Kno, Nina and Lorin Rosen, 2005, undated; 205993 (Box 13, Folder 152)
    - Knox, Sonia, 1981; 205994 (Box 13, Folder 153)
    - Koh, Germaine/National Gallery of Canada, 1995; 205995 (Box 13, Folder 154)
    - Komar and Melmid, 1995; 205996 (Box 13, Folder 155)
    - Komlosi, Alexander, 2000-2003; 205997 (Box 13, Folder 156)
    - Komnenic, Dusanka, 2006; 205998 (Box 13, Folder 157)
    - Korn, Henry, 1984-1986; 205999 (Box 13, Folder 158)
    - Kos, Joe, 159; 206000 (Box 13, Folder 159)
    - Kouns, Marjorie, 2003; 206001 (Box 13, Folder 160)
    - [Kovanuk] family, 1987; 206002 (Box 13, Folder 161)
    - Kozloff, Joyce, 1985-2002, undated; 206003 (Box 13, Folder 162)
    - Krall, Lisa and Edward Bahlman, 1991; 206004 (Box 13, Folder 163)
    - Krarup, Helge, 2001; 206005 (Box 13, Folder 164)
    - Krais, Lea, 1995; 206006 (Box 13, Folder 165)
    - Kreiling, Amy, 2005; 206007 (Box 13, Folder 166)
    - Kresler, Lillian, 1984-1989; 206008 (Box 13, Folder 167)
    - Krigbaum, Megan, 2002; 206009 (Box 13, Folder 168)
    - Krims, Les, undated; 206010 (Box 13, Folder 169)
    - Kris, undated; 206011 (Box 13, Folder 170)
    - Krolack, Karn, 2002; 206012 (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - Krochmal, Walter, 1992; 206013 (Box 13, Folder 172)
    - Kroezen, Jill, 1976; 206014 (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1978, undated; 206015 (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Krulick, Barbara and Eileen Guggenheim/ New York Academy of Art, 1996; 206016 (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - Kuffler, Suzanne, 1985-2006, undated; 206017 (Box 13, Folder 176)
    - Kulick, Sharon, 1972-2005, undated; 206018 (Box 13, Folder 177)
    - Kulterman, Udo, 1983-1988; 206019 (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - Kunin, Julia, 2003; 206020 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - Kurnos, Jill, 1965; 206021 (Box 13, Folder 180)
    - Kurtis, Luke, 2000; 206022; contains CD (Box 13, Folder 181)
    - L, undated; 206023 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - L. E., 1984; 206024 (Box 13, Folder 183)
    - L.M., 1984; 206025 (Box 13, Folder 184)
    - L. Barbara, undated; 206026 (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - LaBerteaux, Hannah, 2005; 206027 (Box 13, Folder 186)
    - Labowitz, Leslie and Suzanne Lacy, undated; 206028 (Box 13, Folder 187)
    - Lacey, Suzanne, 1976-2008, undated; 206029 (Box 13, Folder 188)
    - Lady Pink, 1986; 206030 (Box 13, Folder 189)
    - Lahr, Christin, 1995; 206031 (Box 13, Folder 190)
    - Lamarre, Paul and Melissa Wolf, 1995; 206032 (Box 13, Folder 191)
    - Lance, Dean/ Video Data Bank, 1991-1992; 206041 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lance, Dean, 1996; 206042 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Lane, Barbara, 1991; 206043 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Lang, Avis, 1989; 206044 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Lanyon, Ellen, 1989-1996, undated; 206045 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Lanz, 2001; 206046 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Lanzillotto, Annie, 1997-2003, undated; 206047 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - The Lapp Princess, 1983; 206048 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Laren, 1978; 206049 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Larry, 1998; 206050 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Larsen, Sandee, 1992; 206051 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - LaTourette, Harvey, 1976-1977; 206052 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - [Laura], undated; 206053 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Lauren, 1980, illegible; 206054 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Lauren/ Ms. Magazine, 1996, undated; 206055 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Lauridsen, Hanne, 1987; 206056 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Lawton, Linda, 1976; 206057 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Loue, Marjorie, 2005; 206058 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Lawrence, Matthew, 1993; 206059 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Lawrence, Paula Fried, 1986; 206060 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Lawrence, Paula S., 1990-2000; 206061 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Lawrie, Karen, 1986; 206062 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Lazer Park, 2000; 206063 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Lea, 1988, illegible; 206064 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Leah, undated; 206065 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Leatherdale, Marcus, 1985; 206066 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Leda, Ann, 1997; 206067 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Lederman, Stephanie Brody, 1986-2007; 206068 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Lee and Barbara, 1990; 206069 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Lees, Ming Wei, 1997; 206070 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Leeser, Peter/Northwest Natural, 1994; 206071 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Leeser, Thomas and Alison Saar, 1989-1997; 206072 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Leeser, Tom and Cal Arts Integrated Media, 2007; 206073 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Leeson, Lynn Hershmann, 2007; 206074 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Lefever, Odie, 1990; 206075 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Leff, Gabby, undated; 206076 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Left, Sarah, 2001; 206077 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Leftoverz, 1977; 206078 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Lehmann, Carola, 2005; 206079 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Lehmann, Minnette, 1994; 206080 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Lehrer, Jennifer, 1989; 206081 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Lehrer, Phyllis and Richard, 1991; 206082 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Leila, undated; 206083 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Leo, Vince, undated; 206084 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Lencek, Bibi, 1985-1986; 206085 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Lens, Bob, 1974; 206086 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Lerner, Adam/The Lab, 2006; 206087 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Leroy, A., 1986; 206088 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Lescher, Nita, 1988; 206089 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Leslie, David, 1987-2005; 206090 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Leslie, 2001; 206091 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Letters to the Editor, The New York Times, 1995-2004; 206092 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Levine, Les, 1991; 206093 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Levine, Roberta, undated; 206094 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Levine, Sam, 2008; 206095 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Lewenz, Lisa, 1983-2007; 206096 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Lewis, Jessie Jane, 1994; 206097 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Li, Hanquan/China Workers' Center for International Exchange, 2007; 206099 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Libow, Sue, 1985; 206100 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Lichty, Stephen, 2006, undated; 206101 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Lieberman, Claire, 1988; 206102 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Linden, Amy, 1992; 206103 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Linn, Nancy/Printed Matter, 1987, undated; 206104 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Lipnack, Jessica, 2000; 206105 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Lippard, Lucy, 1972-2005; 206106 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Lisa, 1983; 206107 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Lisa, 1988; 206108 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Liss, Fred, 1982-1984; 206109 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Lissa, 1978, undated; 206110 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - List, Larry, 2002 and date illegible; 206111 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Lister, Ardele, 1978-2003; 206112 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Livingston, Dr. and Mre. P.O., 1982; 206113 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Livingston-Broome, Helen, 1991; 206114 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Liz, 1984, undated; 206115 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Lloyd, Gary, undated; 206116 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Lock and Ally, 1998; 206117 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Locke, Charmaine, Splendora/Huston and James Sarls, undated; 206118 (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Logemann, Jand and Gerry Rosen, 1976; 206119 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Logue, Alexandra/Baruch College, 2000; 206120 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Lolo, Lulu, 1998; 206121 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Long, Mary Ellen, 1985; 206122 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Louis Comfort Tiffany Foundation, 2005; 206123 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Carey Lovelace, 1996-2003; 206124 (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - Lovelinks, Valentine, 1982; 206125 (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - Lovett, Ann, 1990; 206126 (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - Lovett, Laura, 1986; 206127 (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council/Greta Gunderson, 2002-2005; 206128 (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - Lubousky, Susan, 1988; 206129 (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - Lucy, 1978-1984, date illegible; 206130 (Box 14, Folder 89)
    - Lucy and Becky, 1978; 206131 (Box 14, Folder 90)
    - Ludwig, Tiffany, 2000-2006; 206132 (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - Lyle, Joanne, 1978; 206133 (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - Lynn, 1983; 206134 (Box 14, Folder 93)
    - Lynch, Ron/ The Institute for Art and Urban Resources, 1982; 206135 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - Lyon, Jessa, 2007; 206136 (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - Lyons, Joan, 1998; 206137 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - M, 1979-1980; 206138 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    - M, 1983; 206139 (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - M, 1989; 206140 (Box 14, Folder 99)
    - M, 1989; 206141 (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - M, 1995; 206142 (Box 14, Folder 101)
    - M, undated; 206143 (Box 14, Folder 102)
    - M/ Heathcote Art Foundation, 1995; 206144 (Box 14, Folder 103)
    - M + W, date illegible; 206145 (Box 14, Folder 104)
    - M. B., 1976; 206146 (Box 14, Folder 105)
    - M. [ Hashs], date illegible; 206147 (Box 14, Folder 106)
    - Mabe, Joni, 1986-2003; 206148 (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - Mac, Taylor, 2005; 206149 (Box 14, Folder 103)
    - McAllister, Pam/Barbara Deming Memorial Fund, undated; 206150 (Box 14, Folder 104)
    - MacArthur Fellows Program/Daniel Socalow, 2006; 206151 (Box 14, Folder 105)
    - McCarney, Scott, 1998-2006, undated; 206152 (Box 14, Folder 106)
    - McCauley, Robbie, 2000, untitled; 206153 (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - McClurg, John, 1979; 206154 (Box 14, Folder 108)
    - McCray, Kelly and Annette Larson/ Mercer Union, 1996; 206155 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - McDonough, Melissa/ School of the Art Institute of Chicago, undated; 206156 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - McGill, Dominic, 1995-2000; 206157 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - McGinnis, Mark, 1989; 206159 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - McGough, Laura, 1999-2007; 206160 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - McGrath, Diane, 1986; 206162 (Box 14, Folder 114)
    - McKeon, Tom, 1986; 206163 (Box 14, Folder 115)
    - McKenna, Rebecca, 2002; 206164 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - McKereghan, Dan, 2005; 206165 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - McLaughlin, Jean, 1993; 206166 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    - McLaughlin, Thom/USF, 1997, undated; 206167 (Box 14, Folder 119)
    - MacLennan, Alistair, 2006; 206168 (Box 14, Folder 120)
    - MacLennan, Toby, illegible; 206169 (Box 14, Folder 121)
    - McMahon, Paul, 1973-1997, undated; 206170 (Box 14, Folder 122)
    - McNeil/Tucker, 1987; 206171 (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - Macrobiotic Association of Connecticut, 1992; 206172 (Box 14, Folder 124)
    - Magee, Jennifer and Champe Smith, 2008; 206173 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - Maghocco, Lavinia and Stanley Mass, 2005; 206174 (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - Mah, Angela/Daina, 2007; 206175 (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - Maine College of Art/Christine Vincent, 2003; 206176 (Box 14, Folder 128)
    - Mainwaring, Martha, 1981-1984; 206177 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - Mailwald, Carl, 1964; 206178 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - Maiwald, Christa and Mark Segal, 2000-2006; 206179 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - Malatesta, John, 2006; 206180 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - Malcolm, 1993; 206181 (Box 14, Folder 133)
    - Malen, Lenore, 1993; 206182 (Box 14, Folder 134)
    - Malenky, Eda and Alan Rosner, undated; 206183 (Box 14, Folder 135)
    - Malloy, Judy, 1981; 206184 (Box 14, Folder 136)
    - Malpede, John, 1979-1987; 206185 (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - Mandel, Carol/New York University, 2003-2007; 206186 (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - Mandel, Mike, 1976; 206187 (Box 14, Folder 139)